cspro.org 2008-06-23

# Privacy Policy - CSPro

You can access and browse our Web sites without disclosing your personal data. Our Web sites do not let our visitors communicate with other visitors or post information to be accessed by others. Our Web sites do not include links to third-party Web service providers. We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organizations. 

We do not automatically log personal data. We do not link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. 

We do not use cookies to store personal data. We do not link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. 

We collect only the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. For the purposes of customer administration, we collect name and organizational information, including the following: 

  * Organization name 
  * Job title 
  * Address 
  * Contact information 

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources. We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than customer administration. 

**Children's Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children. We do not take specific steps to protect the privacy of children who disclose their personal data to us. 

**Confidentiality/Security**

We do not give visitors to our Web site the option of using a secure transmission method to send us their personal data. We have implemented security policies, rules, and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from: 

  * Unauthorized access 
  * Improper use or disclosure 
  * Unauthorized modification 
  * Unlawful destruction or accidental loss 

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation. All our employees and data processors who have access to and are associated with the processing of personal data are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. 

**Access to the Personal Data We May Hold About You**

To ask whether we keep personal data about you or to request a copy of your personal data, contact us at: 

E-mail: [archive@orcmacro.com](mailto:archive@orcmacro.com)  
Phone: (301) 572-0851   

We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data that we keep about you within 5 working days, free of charge (proof of your identity may be required). We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data: 

  * Erased 
  * Rectified or amended 
  * Completed 

**Privacy Compliance**

No national laws, national self-regulatory schemes, global or regional regulatory schemes, or global self-regulatory schemes are applicable to our Web site or organization. 

**Privacy Support**

If you have an inquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact: 

ORC Macro Data Archive  
11785 Beltsville Drive  
Calverton, MD 20705-3119

Phone: (301) 572-0851  
Fax: (301) 572-0999  
E-mail: [archive@orcmacro.com](mailto:archive@orcmacro.com)
